Guide to the Benoit Mandelbrot Papers M1857
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 8. Research Articles and Other Writings
  - The varying volatility of prices, plainly visualized (heavily edited drafts) (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - What is the shape of Britain? The relief of islands, their coastlines, and the number-area rule, circa 1974 (clean and lightly edited drafts) (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - What will remain of 20th century formal science? - Europaisches Forum 1992, Austria (heavily edited handwritten/computer printout drafts) (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Where fractals/multifractals meet the internet (edited computer printouts) (Box 221, Folder 16)
  - Why is nature fractal and when should noises by scaling? BBM and Richard Voss (heavily edited handwritten/computer printout drafts), 1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Word frequencies and the log-normal function (clean typescript), 1963 May 15 (Box 221, Folder 17)
  - Word frequencies and Markovian discourse (heavily edited draft) (Box 221, Folder 18)
  - Word frequencies and Markovian models of discourse (notes, drafts) (Box 235, Folders 11-12)
  - Misc handwritten drafts, notes, and computer printout drafts, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Annotated proofs and drafts for miscellaneous articles, circa 1968-1995 (Box 498, Folders 1-6)
  - Miscellaneous magazines; articles by or relating to Mandelbrot/fractals, circa 1983-2004 (Box 499, Folders 5-10)
  - Macro-Statistical Models, typescript (Box 501, Folder 10)
  - Quilet (encyclopedia), 1989 (Box 501, Folder 11)
  - Encyclopaedia Universalis, 1978-1980 (Box 501, Folder 13)
  - Chapters from various books (Box 502, Folder 1)
  - Drafts, 1963 (Box 502, Folders 2-3)
  - Miscellaneous drafts (Box 502, Folders 3-9)
  - Articles by BBM (Flat-box 348, Folder 3)
- Series 9. Working files/Research, circa 1948-2000s
  This series consists of the working files of Benoit Mandelbrot. Included are miscellaneous drafts and partial drafts of articles (sometimes with edits and annotations), newspaper and magazine clippings, reprints and photocopies of articles by others, handwritten notes and correspondence.
  This series provides unique insight into the work habits of Mandelbrot -- from the state and nature of his papers and how they were stored, we can infer that he would often work on a number of manuscript drafts at a time, and intersperse clippings, correspondence and other material between unrelated drafts from around the same time period.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Working Files - postcards, cartoon, clippings, brochures, notes, articles by others, circa 1948-2011 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - drafts - Paris, 1950-1952 (Box 76, Folders 1-2)
  - Working Files - drafts - Paris, 1952 (typescript and handwritten drafts) (Box 76, Folders 3-8)
  - Working Files - loose manuscript and typescript notes from box labeled "Old Bits - Paris" [University of Paris?], circa 1952 (Box 97, Folders 1-11)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - Statistiques du Greco de Geneve, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - Saussure (typescript/manuscript notes), 1950s (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - partial drafts of unidentified articles, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - Spectres (typescript/manuscript notes), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - Gibbs Paradox (loose handwritten notes), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - irreversible (loose handwritten notes), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - configuration (loose typescript/handwritten notes), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - divisibility (loose typescript/handwritten notes), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - self-divisible (loose typescript/handwritten notes), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Working Files - Linguistics - miscellaneous loose typescript/handwritten notes, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 98, Folders 9-11)
  - Working Files - Macro-Linguistic miscellany - loose typescript/handwritten notes, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 98, Folders 12-15)
  - Working Files - Macro Linguistic miscellany - loose typescript/handwritten notes, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 99, Folders 1-4)
  - Working Files - figures/tables, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - "Old Activity Reports," circa 1950s-1970s (Box 99, Folders 6-7)
  - Working Files - article/partial article drafts, newspaper/magazine clippings, reprints by others, reprints by BBM, correspondence, notes (loose, handwritten), data, graphs/plots, 1950s-2009 (from hanging files in BBM's apartment - original order maintained) (Box 173, Folders 2-6)
  - Working Files - article/partial article drafts, newspaper/magazine clippings, reprints by others, reprints by BBM, correspondence, notes (loose, handwritten), data, graphs/plots, 1950s-2009 (from hanging files in BBM's apartment - original order maintained) (Box 174, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - misc. clippings/publications by others, 1950s-2000s (Box 145, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - Turbulence - Ithiel de Sola Pool (handwritten notes, data, plots, correspondence), 1961 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - draft JB paper and Fama[?] comments and bit of 1962 book (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Working Files - Turbulence - plots of order size and interdemand times, circa 1963 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Working Files - misc. manuscripts, notes and correspondence on BBM's desktop at IBM, 1966-1971 (Box 59, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - killed proof of 1967 PGIT paper (Noises wiht an 1/fb spectrum as a bridge between direct current and white noise) (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Working Files - Turbulence - Pareto ref. (typescript, handwritten notes), circa 1960s (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - Turbulence - Inventory (typescripts, handwritten notes etc.), circa 1960s (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - Turbulence - misc. Pareto (typescripts, handwritten notes etc), circa 1960s (Box 68, Folders 4-5)
  - Working Files - Turbulence - misc. price (typescripts, handwritten notes etc), circa 1960s (Box 68, Folders 6-8)
  - Working Files - Turbulence - Ying (computer printouts of data), circa 1960s (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Working Files - price manuscript (article) drafts and figures, circa 1960s (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - misc. manuscript drafts by BBM and J. R. Wallis (manuscript/typescript/photocopy drafts; edited), c. 1960s (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - Wall Street/ prices news clippings, 1960s (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - Daniel Orr - chapter draft (edited), circa 1960s (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Working Files - examples and approximations, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - diffusion on fractal lattices - multiple trials, random starting point, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - call money, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - bits of Martingale and Long-Run Economics, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Working Files - random inflections, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - some other prices, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - misc. figures - prices, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Working Files - robustness, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Working Files - thermodynamics, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Working Files - statistical mechanics, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Working Files - random inflections - misc., circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Working Files - Martingale, circa 1960s (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Working Files - "Zipf/Bienayme" - edited handwritten and typescript drafts, photocopies, 1960s (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - "Natural Resources" - article/partial article drafts, notes, plots, figures, data, circa 1960s (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1960s-1970s (Box 433, Folders 2-6)
  - Working Files - ffGn, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - "nothing succeeds like," circa 1960s-1970s (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - Noah, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - "Old Talks and Papers," circa 1960s-1970s (Box 99, Folders 8-9)
  - Working Files - "Old Talks and Papers," circa 1960s-1970s (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - "Old Talks and Papers" - Turbulence bibliographies, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - "Old Talks and Papers" - Turbulences, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - "Old Talks and Papers" - Turbulence misc. (partial typescripts, handwritten notes), circa 1960s-1970s (Box 100, Folders 4-7)
  - Working Files - "Old Talks and Papers" - Turbulence misc. (partial typescripts, handwritten notes), circa 1960s-1970s (Box 101, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - "econs" [economics] - notes, article/partial article drafts, plots, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - Lognormal Pareto paper (notes, figures, data/plots), circa 1960s-1970s (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, articles by others, clippings from publications with fractal images (many news/magazine clippings are about fractals and/or mention Mandelbrot), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 101, Folders 4-5)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, articles by others, clippings from publications with fractal images (many news/magazine clippings are about fractals and/or mention Mandelbrot), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 102, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, articles by others, clippings from publications with fractal images (many news/magazine clippings are about fractals and/or mention Mandelbrot), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 103, Folders 1-4)
  - Working Files - Reprints and articles by others, clippings, photocopies, notes etc. circa 1960-2001 (Box 53, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - Reprints and articles by others, clippings, photocopies, notes etc. circa 1960-2001 (Box 54, Folders 1-4)
  - Working Files - reprints/photocopies of articles by others (some with light annotations), correspondence, handwritten notes, etc., circa 1960s-2000s (Box 78, Folders 5-7)
  - Working Files - articles/reprints by others, clippings, partial article/chapter drafts, photocopies, circa 1960s-2000s (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - partial article drafts, notes, figures, circa 1960s-2000s (Box 145, Folders 4-5)
  - Working Files - misc. notes, data plots and correspondence on BBM's desk at IBM, 1970-1972 (Box 59, Folders 8-10)
  - Working Files - misc. notes, data plots and correspondence on BBM's desk at IBM, 1970-1972 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Working files - Stable distribution - Yale, 1971 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - NBER Journal of Economics, circa 1972 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Working Files - R/S Theorems, circa 1972 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Working Files - PNAS 75 files and related stuff (includes typescript copies of What is the Shape of Britain? Fractional Brownian Relief and the Number-Area Law for Islands and original figures) (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Working Files - Lichtenberger, circa 1975 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Working Files - article and chapter drafts, edited (handwritten and computer printout drafts), 1977-1978 (Box 168, Folders 2-8)
  - Working Files - handwritten and computer printout drafts of miscellaneous articles by BBM (edited), 1978-1979 (Box 166, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - handwritten and computer printout drafts of miscellaneous articles by BBM (edited), 1978-1979 (Box 167, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous article drafts and notes by BBM (edited handwritten and computer printout drafts), 1978-1980 (Box 167, Folders 4-6)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous article drafts and notes by BBM (edited handwritten and computer printout drafts), 1978-1980 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - Correspondence, book reviews, articles, photocopies, notes, mailing lists, clippings, calendars of events, reprints (from stacks of loose papers on BBM's desk at IBM) 1978-2008 (Box 26, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - Correspondence, book reviews, articles, photocopies, notes, mailing lists, clippings, calendars of events, reprints (from stacks of loose papers on BBM's desk at IBM) 1978-2008 (Box 27, Folders 1-2)
  - Working Files - Zarembka (notes, article drafts, data), circa 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - formes nouvelles, circa 1970s (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - old dragons, circa 1970s (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - squigs/old misc., circa 1970s (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Working Files - "Bachelier's Life" circa 1970s (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1970s-1980s (Box 423, Folders 1-16)
  - Working Files - drafts/partial drafts (edited), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Working Files - Leonardo - drafts (Malina), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - misc. clippings, 1970s-1980s (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - How not to explain Hurst's Law (manuscript drafts, articles by others), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Working Files - misc. manuscript drafts/partial drafts, notes, c. 1970s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Working Files - misc. manuscript drafts/partial drafts, notes, c. 1970s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Working Files - data plots/graphs, correspondence, notes, reprints, edited article drafts (possibly including early Selecta draft material), circa 1970s-1990s (original order maintained) (Box 60, Folders 2-6)
  - Working Files - data plots/graphs, correspondence, notes, reprints, edited article drafts (possibly including early Selecta draft material), circa 1970s-1990s (original order maintained) (Box 61, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - data plots/graphs, correspondence, notes, reprints, edited article drafts (possibly including early Selecta draft material), circa 1970s-1990s (original order maintained) (Box 62, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - misc. manuscript drafts (manuscript/computer printout drafts; edited), c. 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Working Files - Ian Stewart - Perspectives, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - Leonardo - drafts, circa 1986 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Working Files - article/chapter drafts, correspondence drafts (edited manuscript and computer printout drafts), c. 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folders 4-7)
  - Working Files - article/chapter drafts, correspondence drafts (edited manuscript and computer printout drafts), c. 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, correspondence, articles/reprints by others, brochures, notes, 1988-2002 (Box 214, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, correspondence, articles/reprints by others, brochures, notes, 1988-2002 (Box 215, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - article/chapter drafts (edited manuscript and computer printout drafts; original order maintained), c. 1988 (Box 41, Folders 2-5)
  - Working Files - article/chapter drafts (edited manuscript and computer printout drafts; original order maintained), c. 1988 (Box 42, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - article/chapter drafts (edited manuscript and computer printout drafts; original order maintained), c. 1988 (Box 43, Folders 1-2)
  - Working Files - includes article drafts, notes and correspondence (edited), c. 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folders 3-4)
  - Working Files - misc. newspaper clippings/photocopies of clippings; reprints by others; lecture/program flyers; book reviews, 1989-1992 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Working Files - misc. newspaper clippings/photocopies of clippings; reprints by others; lecture/program flyers; book reviews, 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - includes article drafts, in French (edited manuscript and computer printouts), c. 1980s (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - Adelaide R. Dexter (correspondence, reprints, images), circa 1980s (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Working Files - Met Trans, circa 1980s (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Working Files - Klein (M. Inc)File, 1980s (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Working Files - J A Given, circa 1980s (Box 80, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, articles by others, handwritten notes, conference announcements/ephemera, circa 1980s (Box 103, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - misc. clippings, publications, circa 1980s (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1980s (Box 427, Folders 1-5)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files, 1980s (Box 426, Folders 1-4)
  - Working files – miscellaneous office files; mostly professional correspondence, 1980s (Box 426, Folders 5-21)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous article and chapter drafts (edited), circa 1980s (Box 175, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - articles/clippings/reprints by others, 1980s-1990s (Box 176, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - articles/clippings/reprints by others, 1980s-1990s (Box 177, Folders 1-4)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, articles by others, handwritten notes, conference announcements/ephemera, travel receipts, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 104, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, articles by others, handwritten notes, conference announcements/ephemera, travel receipts, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - misc. newspaper clippings/photocopies of clippings; reprints by others; lecture/program flyers; book reviews; correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - misc. newspaper clippings/photocopies of clippings; reprints by others; lecture/program flyers; book reviews; correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 67, Folders 2-5)
  - Working Files - includes edited article drafts/partial drafts, c. 1980s-1990s (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - includes edited article/chapter drafts (manuscript and compter printouts; original order maintained), c. 1980s-1990s (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Working Files - drafts/partial drafts of articles (edited); correspondence; handwritten notes, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 69, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - drafts/partial drafts of articles (edited); correspondence; handwritten notes, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 70, Folders 1-2)
  - Working Files - misc. mansucript drafts, partial drafts and notes, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - misc. reprints by others; articles about fractals; magazine/journal covers with fractal images, 1980s-1990s (Box 69, Folders 2-4)
  - Working Files - Reprints and magazine/newspaper clippings by others, late 1980s-early 1990s (Box 55, Folders 2-5)
  - Working Files - Reprints and magazine/newspaper clippings by others, late 1980s-early 1990s (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - clippings, correspondence, brochures, announcements, articles by others, 1980s-1990s (Box 197, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - clippings, correspondence, brochures, announcements, articles by others, 1980s-1990s (Box 198, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - articles/clippings/reprints by others, 1980s-2000s (Box 177, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - articles/clippings/reprints by others, 1980s-2000s (Box 178, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous correspondence, clippings, article drafts by BBM, articles by others, 1980s-2000s (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Working files - newspaper/magazine clippings, correspondence, articles/reprints by others, 1980s-2000s (Box 312, Folders 2-5)
  - Working files - newspaper/magazine clippings, correspondence, articles/reprints by others, 1980s-2000s (Box 313, Folders 1-5)
  - Working files - newspaper/magazine clippings, correspondence, articles/reprints by others, 1980s-2000s (Box 314, Folders 1-2)
  - Working Files - loose, handwritten notes, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 216, Folders 1-7)
  - Working Files - misc. loose handwritten notes by BBM, circa 1990 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Working files – Project 1, 1990 (Box 504, Folders 11)
  - Working Files - includes heavily edited article/foreword drafts, some correspondence (manuscript and compter printouts; original order maintained), 1991 (Box 44, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - includes heavily edited article/foreword drafts, some correspondence (manuscript and compter printouts; original order maintained), 1991 (Box 45, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - includes heavily edited article/foreword drafts, some correspondence (manuscript and compter printouts; original order maintained), 1991 (Box 46, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - includes heavily edited article/foreword drafts, some correspondence (manuscript and compter printouts; original order maintained), 1991 (Box 47, Folders 1-2)
  - Working Files - notes, correspondence, data plots/graphs, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous drafts (manuscript and computer printout drafts; some heavily edited), c. 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folders 3-4)
  - Working Files - "misc. correspondence, reprints, 1992-2003" (original order maintained) (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Working Files - "misc. correspondence, reprints, 1992-2003" (original order maintained) (Box 200, Folders 1-6)
  - Working Files - "misc. correspondence, reprints, 1992-2003" (original order maintained) (Box 201, Folders 1-3)
  - Working Files - correspondence, clippings, articles, 1993-2005 (Box 210, Folders 1-8)
  - Working Files - correspondence, clippings, articles, 1993-2005 (Box 211, Folders 1-2)
  - Working Files - correspondence, manuscript drafts of papers with Michael Frame, 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Working Files - news/magazine clippings; manuscript drafts; handwritten notes, 1997-2008 (Box 146, Folders 6-8)
  - Working Files - news/magazine clippings; manuscript drafts; handwritten notes, 1997-2008 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - Correspondence, attachments, clippings, notes, reprints, web article printouts, book lists, book reviews (from stacks of loose papers on BBM's desk at IBM) 1997-2009 (Box 27, Folders 3-5)
  - Working Files - Correspondence, attachments, clippings, notes, reprints, web article printouts, book lists, book reviews (from stacks of loose papers on BBM's desk at IBM) 1997-2009 (Box 28, Folders 1-5)
  - Working Files - Correspondence, attachments, clippings, notes, reprints, web article printouts, book lists, book reviews (from stacks of loose papers on BBM's desk at IBM) 1997-2009 (Box 29, Folders 1-4)
  - Working Files - Correspondence, attachments, clippings, notes, reprints, etc. (from stacks of loose papers on BBM's desk at IBM) 1998-2005 (Box 29, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - Correspondence, attachments, clippings, notes, reprints, etc. (from stacks of loose papers on BBM's desk at IBM) 1998-2005 (Box 30, Folders 1-2)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, correspondence, articles/reprints by others, circa 1999-2004 (original order maintained) (Box 211, Folders 3-7)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, correspondence, articles/reprints by others, circa 1999-2004 (original order maintained) (Box 212, Folders 1-7)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, correspondence, articles/reprints by others, circa 1999-2004 (original order maintained) (Box 213, Folders 1-4)
  - Working files - 1990s (Box 302, Folder 15)
  - Working Files - reprints by others; handwritten notes; correspondence; article drafts (edited), circa 1990s (Box 70, Folders 5-6)
  - Working Files - miscellaneous edited manuscript and computer printout drafts, circa 1990s (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Working Files - drafts of papers with Rudolf H. Riedi, circa 1990s (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Working Files - loose, undated handwritten notes, circa 1990s (Box 64, Folders 6-8)
  - Working Files - drafts/partial drafts of articles (some heavily edited), circa 1990s (Box 80, Folders 5-7)
  - Working Files - newspaper/magazine clippings, articles by others, handwritten notes, internet article printouts, late 1990s (Box 105, Folders 2-8)